(
"ai_sub_version": "3.2.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-10T01:34:36.099768",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 17,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
輪堂千早生誕祭2026 Flat Out Summentes
重大告知あり 2026.7.8 [Wed] 20:00 START
Chihaya Rindou Birthday Celebration 2026: Flat Out Summentes
Major Announcement | Starts July 8, 2026 [Wed] at 20:00
輪堂千速生誕祭2026に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Festival 2026!
盛り上がる準備できてるかー？
Are you ready to get hyped?!
ぶち上げていくぞ！
Let's turn it up!
傷はちょっと今から急いでライブ会場にみんなを連れていかなきゃなんないから、
But I have to hurry and take everyone to the live venue right now...
一緒に行ってくれるか？行くぞ！
...so will you come with me? Let's go!
熱くなった銀のメタリックハート
This silver metallic heart grew hot
導火線に火をつけてあげる
I'll light the fuse for you
不思議なほどハイな気分さ
It's such a wondrously high feeling
砂埃を巻き上げて行こう
Let's kick up some dust and go!
悲鳴をまじらせ暴走する鼓動
The wild pulse mixed with screams
目の前にはミサイルの雨
Before my eyes, a rain of missiles
アドレナリンずっと流して
Keep the adrenaline pumping
僕の方がオーバーヒートしそう
I feel like I'm going to overheat!
爆発して灰になっても
Even if I explode and turn to ash
このままだと笑ってるねきっと
I bet I'll still be laughing just like this
街を追い越してこの世の果てまで
Overtaking the city, all the way to the end of the world
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして!
Let's speed off and perish together, now reach out your hand!
地平線に届くように
To reach the horizon...
限界まで振り切ってくれ
...swing it all the way to the limit!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest Driver's High
最高のフィナーレを! Yeah!
This is the greatest finale! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで僕らは消え失せて
With only a few left to count, we'll vanish...
真暗な朝が来るね
...and a pitch-black morning will come.
お気に入りの服にさぁ着がえたなら保存
If you've changed into your favorite clothes...
駆け出して!
...run out!
あきれるほど声を上げて
Raise your voice to an absurd degree
大気圏を突破しようぜ
Let's break through the atmosphere!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest Driver's High
鋼の翼で
With wings of steel
駆けぬけてよ 時間切れまで
Run through until time runs out
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
'Cuz I was born speed crazy!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest Driver's High
来世でまた会おう Yeah!
Let's meet again in the next life, yeah!
広い宇宙の数ある一つ
One among the countless in the vast universe,
青い地球の広い世界で
in this wide world of the blue Earth,
小さな恋の思いは届く
my feelings of a small love will reach
小さな島のあなたのもとへ
you on your small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Since meeting you, time has passed,
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる...
and the letters filled with my feelings increase.
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before we knew it, we resonated with each other,
時に激しく 時に切なく
sometimes intensely, sometimes painfully.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
The sound echoes far away, to the distant horizon,
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
a gentle song that can change the world.
ほら
Look,
あなたにとって 大事な人ほど
the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただ
I just
あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
want it to reach only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You will realize, and the two of us will walk,
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
even on a dark road, the moon lights our days.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Holding hands tightly, without ever letting go,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
our feelings are strong, promising eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う...
Even at the abyss of eternity, I will surely say
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
the same words, without my feelings changing.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Yet it's not enough; it turns into tears,
喜びになり 言葉にできず
then into joy, and without words,
ただ抱きしめる
I just hold you,
I just hold you.
ほら
Look,
あなたにとって 大事な人ほど
the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただ
I just
あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
want it to reach only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
夢ならば 覚めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake up.
夢ならば 覚めないで...
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の
The time I spent with you...
星となる
...will become an eternal star.
ほら
Look,
あなたにとって 大事な人ほど
the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただ
I just
あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
want it to reach only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
ほら
Look,
あなたにとって 大事な人ほど
the person most important to you
すぐそばにいるの
is right by your side.
ただ
I just
あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
want it to reach only you.
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo.
はぁ〜い！
Heeeey!
というわけで！皆さん、林堂千速生誕祭にお越しくださり
And with that! Everyone, thank you so much for coming...
ありがとうございます！
...to Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Festival!
聞こえていますでしょうか？
Can you all hear me?!
挨拶します！
Let me do my greeting!
エキサイト＆レッツゴー！
Excite & Let's Go!
やばい！
Oh my, I messed up!
ロックなロードのDJ系運転手タレントの林堂千速です！
I'm Rindo Chihaya, the rock 'n' road DJ-style driver talent!
こんちは〜！
Konchihaya!
ということで始まりました！
And with that, it has finally begun!
初めての3D生誕ライブ！
My very first 3D Birthday Live!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get super hyped up together!
配信のハッシュタグは、右上...
The hashtag for this stream is in the top right...
あ、これ、これ、右上、こちらになります！
Ah, here, here, on the top right, this one!
ハッシュタグ林堂千速生誕祭2026になるので
It's hashtag #RindoChihayaBirthdayFes2026,
たくさんポストしていただけると、とっても嬉しいです！
so I'd be super happy if you post a lot!
ちゃんと見ますからね！
I'll definitely be checking them!
ぜひあの、トレンド1位なんかになれたりしたら嬉しいななんて思うので
I'd love it if we could reach number 1 on trending,
いっぱいスクショとかね、貼ってポスト...
so share lots of screenshots and post them...
...お祝いさせてもらえると、嬉しいです！
...I'd be so happy if you could celebrate with me!
わぁ！こんちはや！ありがとう！
Wow! Konchihaya! Thank you!
ということでね、一旦ちょっと
So, for now...
2曲歌わせていただいたので振り返っていこうかなと思うんですが
since I've sung two songs, I thought we could look back on them,
まずは1曲目！「Driver's High」を海沿いを、
but first, the first song! "Driver's High" along the coast,
フブタローでドライブしながら歌わせていただきました！
I got to sing it while driving in the Fubutaro!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
デビューのね、一番最初にL'Arc-en-Cielの曲を歌って、
At my debut, the very first thing I did was sing a L'Arc-en-Ciel song,
で、この「Driver's High」をいつか歌ってほしいってすごい、
and I was told so many times that they wanted me to sing "Driver's High" someday,
いっぱい言われていたので、絶対に生誕で歌おうと思って、1曲目に選びました！
so I definitely wanted to sing it for my birthday, and chose it as the first song!
いや、あの、
Well, um...
まああの、あそこカバーの私有地なので、
well, since that place is Cover's private property,
色々もろもろひっくるめて、OKです！大丈夫！大丈夫！きっと大丈夫！
taking everything into account, it's OK! It's fine! It's fine! I'm sure it's fine!
そして2曲目！「小さな恋のうた」でした！どうでしたでしょうか！
And the second song! It was "Chiisana Koi no Uta"! How was it?
そう、これ！
Yes, this!
千速が弾いてましたよ！
Chihaya was playing it!
いやあの、ご存知の方も多いかなと思いますが、ね、エレキを購入しまして練習していたんですが、
Well, as many of you probably know, I bought an electric guitar and have been practicing,
あの、弾かせていただきました！
and I got to play it!
やっぱりなんか、エレキで初めて挑戦するのってなんか、「小さな恋のうた」だよなってイメージがあって、
Somehow, I had this image that the first song to challenge on electric guitar should be "Chiisana Koi no Uta",
この曲を選んだんですけど、すっごい難しい！
so I chose this song, but it's so difficult!
すっごい難しかったんですけど、でもね、生誕ライブでかっこいいところ見せたかったので、
It was extremely difficult, but I wanted to show a cool side of me at my birthday live,
いっぱい、いっぱい、いっぱい練習して、
so I practiced over and over and over again,
弾けてたよね？なんとか。弾けてたと思います！
And I managed to play it, right? Somehow. I think I was able to play it!
なのでね、いっぱい、あの、後でアーカイブとかも見直して、聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
So, I'd be happy if you could look back at the archive later and listen to it a lot!
ということで、そしてね、お気づきの方もいますが、「小さな恋のうた」最初は体育館だったんですけど、
By the way, some of you may have noticed, but for "Chiisana Koi no Uta", we started in a gym,
外に出ることができましたよ！
but we were able to go outside!
やっぱ夏といえば、外！海！山！自然！
After all, when you think of summer, it's outdoors! The ocean! Mountains! Nature!
そして、夏の音楽といえばフェス！をイメージして、
And when you think of summer music, it's festivals! With that image in mind,
夏フェス会場になっております！
this has become a summer festival venue!
後ろにはね、海もあって、最高のロケーションで、
In the background, there's the ocean, and in this amazing location,
今日はフェスを開催していければなと思っております！
I hope we can hold the festival today!
こんなにね、広いので、あっちに行ったり、あ、ちょっと、予定にない動きをしてすみません、本当に。
It's so spacious, so going over there... ah, sorry for the unplanned movement, really.
こっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています。
I'm planning to go this way and that.
では、まあ、ちょっとあんまり喋るとね、あれなので、次の曲行こうと思うので、
Well, if I talk too much, we won't get to it, so I think I'll move on to the next song.
ちょっと準備するので、ギターとマイク置いてきます。ちょっと待っててね。行ってきます！
I need to prepare, so I'll go put down the guitar and mic. Please wait a bit. Off I go!
はい、ということで！
Alright, so!
はい、来ました、来ました！ということでここからはですね、ゲストブロックになります！
Yes, I'm back, I'm back! So from here on, it will be the guest block!
ので、このあともいっぱい楽しんでいってください！盛り上がっていくぞー！
So please continue to enjoy it to the fullest! Let's get fired up!
GO!!!
We are fighting dreamers
高みを目指して
aiming high
Fighting dreamers
なりふり構わず
don't care what people think
Fighting dreamers
信じるがままに
follow what they believe
Oli oli oli oh-! Just go my way!
Right here right now
Bang! ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー！
Bang! Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now
Burn! ぶった斬ってくぜ get the fire!
Burn! Slash through, get the fire!
Right here right now
Bang! ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー！
Bang! Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now
Burn!
険しい修羅の道の中
In the midst of this steep, harsh path,
他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く？
whose map are you opening to find where you're going?
極彩色のカラスがそれを
A multicolored crow
奪い取って破り捨てた
snatched it away and tore it up
さぁ心の目見開いて
Now, open your mind's eye
しかと今を見極めろ
and take a firm look at the present
失うモノなんてないさ
There is nothing to lose,
いざ参ろう！
so let's go!
We are fighting dreamers
高みを目指して
aiming high
Fighting dreamers
なりふり構わず
don't care what people think
Fighting dreamers
信じるがままに
follow what they believe
Oli oli oli oh-! Just go my way!
Right here right now
Bang! ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー！
Bang! Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now
Burn!
音を立てず忍び寄る影が
The shadow creeping up without a sound
いつも僕らを惑わせる
always leads us astray
有言実行 大きな風が
True to its word, a great wind
うねりを上げて吹き荒れる
rages and swells up
かざした鋭い刃で
Hold a sharp sword up high
己の未来切り開け
and cut a path to your future!
保証なんてどこにもないさ
There are no guarantees anywhere,
なぁそうだろ？
am I right?
We are fighting dreamers
高みを目指して
aiming high
Fighting dreamers
なりふり構わず
don't care what people think
Fighting dreamers
信じるがままに
Just as we believe...
Oli Oli Oli Oh- Just go my way
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー
Right here, right now (Bang!) Shoot like a line drive!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶった切ってくぜ get on fire
Right here, right now (Bang!) Cut through, get on fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー
Right here, right now (Bang!) Shoot like a line drive!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶった切ってくぜ get on fire
Right here, right now (Bang!) Cut through, get on fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers この仲間たちと
We are Fighting Dreamers, with these comrades...
Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
Fighting Dreamers, involving everything...
Fighting Dreamers 志高く
Fighting Dreamers, with high ambitions...
Oli Oli Oli Oh-
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming for the heights...
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, without caring about appearances...
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as we believe...
Oli Oli Oli Oh- Just go my way
Don't forget your first impulse. Go my way
Keep your adventurous spirit, safe back. Go my way
Don't forget your first impulse.
Keep your adventurous spirit, safe back.
GO!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー
Right here, right now (Bang!) Shoot like a line drive!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶった切ってくぜ get on fire
Right here, right now (Bang!) Cut through, get on fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ like a 弾丸ライナー
Right here, right now (Bang!) Shoot like a line drive!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶった切ってくぜ get on fire
Right here, right now (Bang!) Cut through, get on fire!
Bang!
ガラス玉ひとつ落とされた
A single glass marble was dropped.
追いかけてもうひとつ落っこちた
Chasing after it, another dropped down.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに
In a sunny spot meant for just one,
ひとつだけ残ってる
only one remains.
心臓が始まった時
The moment our hearts began to beat,
嫌でも人は場所を取る
like it or not, people take up space.
奪われない様に
To prevent it from being snatched away,
守り続けてる
they keep protecting it.
汚さずに保ってきた手でも
Even with hands kept clean until now,
汚れて見えた
they looked dirty.
記憶を疑う前に
Before doubting my memory,
記憶に疑われてる
I'm being doubted by my memory.
必ず僕らは出会うだろう
We will surely meet each other,
同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
using the sound of the same heartbeat as our landmark.
ここに居るよ
I am right here,
いつだって呼んでるから
because I'm always calling for you.
くたびれた理由が重なって揺れる時
When worn-out motives overlap and tremble,
生まれた意味を知る
we learn the meaning of our birth.
存在が続く限り
As long as our existence continues,
仕方無いから場所を取る
there's no choice but to take up space.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに
In a sunny spot meant for just one,
ふたつはちょっと入れない
two can't really fit.
ガラス玉ひとつ落とされた
A single glass marble was dropped.
落ちた時 何か弾き出した
When it fell, it pushed something out.
奪い取った場所で
In the place that was snatched away,
光を浴びた
it bathed in the light.
信じたって手放した物
The things I let go of despite believing,
気付けば数字でしかない
when I realized, were nothing but numbers.
名前が無いものは
Things that have no name
どうやら1と0の間
seem to exist between 1 and 0.
初めて僕らは出会うだろう
For the first time, we will meet each other,
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
using the flag of the same scream as our landmark.
忘れないで
Please don't forget,
いつだって呼んでるから
because I'm always calling for you.
重ねた理由を二人で埋める時
When we fill in our overlapped reasons together,
約束が果たされる
our promise will be fulfilled.
鏡なんだ
We are a mirror to each other,
僕ら互いに
each of us reflecting
それぞれのカルマを
our respective karma.
映すための
For reflecting it,
汚れた手と手で触り合って
touching each other with dirty hands,
形が分かる
we can understand its shape.
ここに居るよ
I am right here,
確かに触れるよ
I can certainly touch you,
ひとり分の陽だまりに
in a sunny spot meant for just one,
僕らは居る
the two of us are there.
忘れないで
Please don't forget,
いつだって呼んでるから
because I'm always calling for you.
同じガラス玉の内側の方から
From the inside of the very same glass marble.
そうさ必ず
That's right, surely,
僕らは出会うだろう
we will meet each other.
沈めた理由に十字架を立てる時
When we erect a cross upon our sunken reasons,
約束は果たされる
our promise will be fulfilled.
僕らはひとつになる
We will become one.
カルマ
[Title: Karma]
じぶんROCK
[Title: Jibun ROCK]
今日も君は
Today, you also...
信じること 忘れずに目覚められているか？
...are you awake without forgetting to believe?
時が経つと
As time passes...
自分さえも 信じられなくなる時代なのです
...is it an era where you can't even believe in yourself?
自分では気付かないの
I don't realize it myself,
がこの症状の特徴で
and that's the characteristic of this symptom.
唯一ある予防法は
The only way to prevent it...
自分に嘘だきゃつかないこと
...is to not tell lies to yourself.
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
Don't you ever forget it!!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I'm not me anymore,
たとえ生きてたって
even if I lived,
生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ
I wouldn't find the meaning of living.
声にならない叫びは
The scream that can't become a voice,
僕が声を枯らして
I'll lose my voice...
叫んで歌って
...shouting and singing,
伝わるまでわめいて
crying out until it reaches you,
届くまで止めない！！
I won't stop until it reaches you!
今日も地球は回り続ける
Today, the earth continues to spin,
誰が泣いても怒っても止まらず
never stopping no matter who cries or gets angry.
試しに僕が風邪をひいても
Even if I were to catch a cold as a test,
もちろん止まることなんてねえわ
of course it would never stop.
人生も同じように
Life is the exact same way,
止まることはなく進んでいくから
it keeps moving forward without stopping.
だからそうさ今日も人は
So that's why today, people once again
お手手のシワとシワをあわせんの
press their hands together in prayer.
終わらせちまう事なんか
Ending things...
誰にだってできんだろ？
...is something anyone can do, right?
たとえ終わっちまったって
Even if it comes to an end,
次のスタート すぐ切れんだろ？！
you can start anew right away, can't you?!
今君が思うキセキも
Even the miracle you're thinking of right now,
底上げさせてしまえば
if you raise its baseline,
もうその時点でそのキセキは
at that very moment, that miracle...
君にとっちゃ必然のお仲間さ
...becomes an inevitable companion to you.
WOW!!
何回ダメダメと言われようが
No matter how many times they say 'no, no',
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
practically speaking, that doesn't matter.
今自分自身
Right now, within yourself,
必要なものたくわえてそろえとけよ
gather and prepare what you need!
なぁそうだろ？！
Hey, isn't that right?!
まだまだ時間はまだあるぞ
There's still, still time left.
先見の明 今は研ぎ澄まして
Hone your foresight right now,
主人公は一人だけ
There's only one main character.
自分の物語のはじまり
It's the start of your own story!
星座になれたら
[Title: If I Could Become a Constellation]
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock is almost 6
もうそこに一番星
There's already the first star
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on shadows, wanting to blend into the night on the way home
どんなに探してみても
No matter how much I search
一つしかない星
There's only one star
...億光年
...billion light-years
離れたところから
from away,
あんなに
shining so...
輝く
...brightly.
いいな 君は
It must be nice, you are
みんなから愛されて
loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕はずっと
"No, I've always been...
一人きりさ」
...all alone."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜
on a night of falling stars,
一瞬の願いごと
my wish for a split second...
きらめいて
...would sparkle,
ゆらめいて
and waver,
震えてるシグナル
as a trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて
looking up at the sky,
指を指されるような
as if being pointed at,
つないだ線 解かないで
please don't undo our connected lines,
僕がどんなに 眩しくても
no matter how dazzling I might be.
もうすぐ時計は8時
The clock is almost at eight,
夜空に満天の星
with a sky full of stars in the night.
何億光年
Billions of light-years...
離れたところには
...away,
もう ないかもしれない保存用
they might not even exist anymore.
月が
The moon...
綺麗で
...is so beautiful,
泣きそうになるのは
the reason it makes me want to cry
いつの
is because
日にか
someday,
別れが来るから
parting will surely come.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
彗星みたい
like a comet,
流れるひとりごと
a passing murmur...
消えていく
...would fade away,
残像は
leaving an afterimage
真夜中のプリズム
as a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my earnest wish could reach someone,
変われるかな
I wonder if I could change,
夜の淵を
even someone like me,
なぞるような
who merely traces
こんな僕でも
the edge of the night.
遥か彼方
In the far distance,
僕らは出会ってしまった
we ended up meeting each other.
カルマだから
Because it's karma,
何度も出会ってしまうよ
we'll keep meeting again and again.
雲の隙間で
Through the gaps in the clouds...
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう 絵空事
let's spread the night and paint an illusion,
暗闇を
to light up
照らすような
the darkness,
満月じゃ
even if it's
なくても
not a full moon.
だから集まって星座になりたい保存用
That's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
releasing a colorful light.
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't undo our connected lines,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you might be.
はい！ということで
Yes! And with that...
FGLちゃーん！保存用
FGL!
イェーイ！
Yay!
聴いてくれてありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for listening!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫。息整えてね。
I'm okay, I'm okay. Catch your breath.
あの、FGLでね、ずっとバンドがやりたいと、思っていたので
Um, I've always wanted to do a band as FGL,
まぁ今日はちょっと、エアバンドなんですけれどもね、みんなで「星座になれたら」披露させていただきました！
so although it's just an air-band today, we got to perform "Seiza ni Naretara" together!
楽しかったー！ありがとうー！
That was so much fun! Thank you!
じゃ一回、自己紹介しとくか。オッケー！じゃあ、りっちゃんから、いつもの自己紹介、お願いします！
Let's introduce ourselves. Okay! Ricchan, please go ahead with your usual introduction!
はーい！私の歌に合図！揺れるようなエンドレス！フローグロウの...
Hi! A signal to my song! Like a shaking endless! Flow Glow's...
キュートで無軌道なベース担当、響咲リカです！
...cute and reckless bassist, Isaki Rika!
ベース弾いてるリカちゃん、かっこいいよ！
Rika-chan playing the bass is so cool!
ちーちゃん、お誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy birthday, Chi-chan!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして！にこたんが来た！フローグロウの...保存用
And! Niko-tan has arrived! Flow Glow's...
なんだっけ、あれ。
What was it again?
キーボード！
Keyboards!
フローグロウのキーボード担当、虎金妃にこ、にこたんだよー！
Flow Glow's keyboardist, Koganei Niko, aka Niko-tan!
にこたん、ありがとうー！
Thank you, Niko-tan!
はーい、ひ弱、インドア、スタミナ足りない、フローグロウの...ドラム担当、水宮りこです！
Hi! Weak, indoor-loving, lacking stamina... Flow Glow's drummer, Mizumi Liko!
ドラム担当！
The drummer!
ちー、お誕生日おめでとうー！
Chi, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして！
And next...
せーの！
One, two...
うー、りおな！
Woo, Riona!
いつもキラキラな
The always sparkling...
キ、キララ、ビビです！
I'm Ki-Kirara Vivi!
あ、忘れてた。ビビはギター担当！
Oh, I forgot. Vivi is in charge of guitar!
じゃじゃじゃじゃーん
Tah-dah!
足引っ張ってるよね
You're holding us back, aren't you?
なるほどね
I see, I see.
ちは、お誕生日おめでとう！
Chiha, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、ということで、みんな来てくれてありがとう！
So anyway, thank you everyone for coming!
なんかいいお知らせがあるんじゃないの？
Don't you have some good news for us?
なんと、トレンド1位になったらしいです！
What do you know, we apparently reached #1 on trending!
やったー！嬉しい！すごい！
Yay! I'm so happy! Amazing!
ちはやって2文字だから、あの、トレンドに乗らねえのよ。
You see, "Chiha" is only two characters, so it wouldn't trend.
あー、なるほどね。
Ah, I see.
だから乗ったらいいなと思ってたんだけど、こんな誕生日に嬉しいプレゼントをいただきまして、本当にありがとうございました。
So I was hoping it would trend, and getting such a wonderful birthday present makes me so happy. Thank you so much.
みんながいっぱいツイートしてくれたんだよね。ありがとう！もっと呟いてね。
Everyone tweeted so much for us. Thank you! Keep tweeting!
はい、ということで、生配信、いかがでしたか？皆さん、どうでしたか？
Yes, so how did you like the live stream so far, everyone?
楽しかった！
It was fun!
ドラムも叩きたくなりました。
It made me want to play the drums too.
叩いてたよね、ドラムで。経験者なんだよね。
You were playing them, weren't you? Since you have experience.
そうなんですよね、実は。
Actually, yes, I do.
だから、いつかFGバンドをね、
So, someday, an FG Band...
絶対できる、できる！
We can definitely do it, we can!
結成したいの。ちょっと今回は、エアバンドだったので、にこたんにキーボードを担当していただいたんですけど...
I want to form one. Since it was an air band this time, we had Nikotan play the keyboard...
すごかったでしょ？
It was amazing, wasn't it?
すごかった、本当にすごかった！
It was, it really was amazing!
片手で弾いてたもんね。
I was playing with one hand.
すごーい！全然手動いてたもんね。そういうことよね。
Amazing! Your hands were totally moving. Indeed.
何でもできるね。一歩も触れずにね。
You can do anything. Without even touching it once!
ちはもすごい楽しかったし、みんなも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです。いつか実現させましょう！
I had a lot of fun, and I'm so glad everyone enjoyed it too. Let's make it a reality someday!
したい！やりたい！
I want to! Let's do it!
そんな時はみんな、今回の楽器でいいんですか？
At that time, is everyone fine with using their current instruments?
あれ？違う楽器がやりたいって？
Wait, do you want to play a different instrument?
歌、歌う！
I'll sing!
歌はダメ！喧嘩になるから！
No singing! We'll end up fighting!
にこたんはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Nikotan, if you were to play, what instrument would you want?
え、だって何でもいいよ。もう出まくってるよね、もうね。
Well, anything is fine. I'm already out there, you know?
ギター？今ギター、ギター、ドラム、ベースがあるんだけど...
Guitar? Right now we have guitar, guitar, drums, bass...
そしたらやっぱりキーボードしかないよね。
In that case, it has to be keyboard, right?
私、バイオリン弾ける！バイオリン、バイオリン！
I can play the violin! Violin, violin!
これがあるじゃん、これがある。
We have this!
いや、ちょっと違う気がするけど、バイオリン入ってるバンドめっちゃかっこいいよ。
No, I feel like that's a bit different, but a band with a violin is really cool.
打楽器がどう？トライアングルとか。
How about percussion? Like a triangle.
ビビはトライアングル...
Vivi on triangle...
ビビはタンバリンでいいよ、タンバリン。
Vivi can do the tambourine, tambourine.
全員で打楽器バンド！
All of us as a percussion band!
ビビ、トライアングルでそれ以外はシンバルとか。
Vivi on triangle, and others on cymbals, etc.
全然違うジャンルになるからやめて、それ。
It'll be a totally different genre, so stop that!
でも、そういうのもやってみたい！楽しそう。
But I'd like to try something like that too! It looks fun.
FGの企画とかでやったりするのね。
We could do it as an FG project.
確かに！やろうやろう！やりましょう！
True! Let's do it!
ということでね、今回はFGちゃんたちに来ていただきまして、本当に今日はね、長い時間、リハーサルから付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
So, we had the FG members join us today. Thank you so much for spending so much time with me, starting from rehearsals!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations!
これは、ちはが何でもします券を皆様に贈呈いたします。
This means I shall present you all with a "Chiha will do anything" ticket.
え？！何でもって言った？！
Wait, did you say anything?!
何でもいいの？とりあえず一枚？
Anything? For now, one ticket?
一枚。いただきっ！あ、待って、取り消し！取り消し！取り消し券なし！
One ticket. Thank you! Ah, wait, cancel! Cancel! No cancel ticket!
美味しいご飯ごちそうさまです！
Thanks for the delicious meal!
それはもちろん、全員に奢らせていただきます。
Of course, I'll treat everyone to that.
やった、よかったー。ごちそうさまです！
Yay, glad to hear that. Thank you for the meal!
今日もお弁当豪華だったしね。
The bento was luxurious today too, wasn't it?
お弁当、奮発しました。喜んでいただけてよかったです。
I splurged on the bento. I'm glad you liked it.
まだあるので持って帰ってください。
There are still some left, so please take them home.
はーい！
Okay!
ではね、そろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います！
Now, it's about time to move on to the next song!
みんなも見ててくれるかな？
Will everyone watch us too?
ばっちり見てるよ！
We'll definitely watch!
では、ライブ見てくれてるみんなも、まだまだ盛り上がっていってくださいね！
Then, everyone watching the live stream, please keep the excitement going!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まだコメント欄は「なんでも」って言ってる。
The comment section is still saying "anything".
まだ何でも？まだそこにいる？
Still "anything"? Are they still on that?
すぐに帰ろうとしないで。
Don't try to leave so quickly.
リスナーさんたちには何もしないですけど、FGちゃんたちには何でもしたい気持ちでいますよ、もちろん。
I won't do anything for the listeners, but of course, I want to do anything for the FG girls.
やったー！
Yay!
それくらいの愛はあります。
I have that much love for you.
気持ちだけじゃなくてね。お願いします。
Not just in feelings, please.
やばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no!
ということで、みんな、はい、バイバイ！
So everyone, okay, bye-bye!
バイバイ！ありがとうね！
Bye-bye! Thank you!
俺も一緒に行こう。しゅっ、しゅっ、しゅっ...
I'll go with you too. Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh...
打上花火 / 作詞・作曲: 米津玄師
Uchiage Hanabi / Lyrics & Music: Kenshi Yonezu
あの日見渡した渚を
I still remember the shore we looked over that day
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it even now
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words etched on the sand
君の後ろ姿
The sight of your back
寄り返す波が
The returning waves
足元をよぎり
cross my feet,
何かを攫う
taking something away.
夕凪の中
In the evening calm,
日暮れだけが通り過ぎて行く
only the sunset passes by.
パッと光って咲いた
Suddenly blooming with a flash,
花火を見ていた
we were watching the fireworks.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, a summer that won't end yet...
曖昧な心を
Melting our ambiguous hearts,
解かして繋いだ
and connecting us,
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to continue.
あと何度君と同じ
How many more times with you
花火を見られるかなって
can I watch the same fireworks?
笑う顔に何が出来るだろうか
What can I do for that smiling face?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと
Getting hurt, feeling joy,
繰り返す波と情動
repeating waves and emotions,
焦燥 最終列車の音
impatience, the sound of the last train.
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll call your name over and over,
波間を選び もう一度
choosing the waves, once more...
もう二度と悲しまずに
so we never have to be sad again,
済むように
ever again.
ハッと息を飲めば
If I catch my breath,
消えちゃいそうな光が
the light that seems about to fade
きっとまだ胸に沈んでいた
was surely still lingering in my heart.
手を伸ばせば触れた
If I reach out, I could touch
温かい未来は
the warm future...
密かに二人を夢見た
secretly dreamed of the two of us.
パッと花火が
Suddenly, the fireworks
夜に咲いた
bloomed in the night,
夜に咲いて
blooming in the night,
静かに消えた
and quietly faded away.
離れないで
Don't leave me,
もう少しだけ
just a little longer...
もう少しだけ このままで
just a little longer, like this.
あの日の見渡した渚を
The shore we looked out over that day,
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it even now.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words carved into the sand,
君の後ろ姿
your figure from behind.
パッと光って咲いた
Suddenly blooming with a flash,
花火を見ていた
we were watching the fireworks.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely, a summer that won't end yet...
曖昧な心を
Melting our ambiguous hearts,
解かして繋いだ
and connecting us,
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to continue.
ららら...
La la la...
ソラニン
Solanin
思い違いは空のかなた
Our misunderstandings are far beyond the sky.
さよならだけの人生か
Is this life just a series of goodbyes?
ほんの少しの未来は見えたのに
Even though I could see a little bit of our future...
たのに
...even though...
さよならなんだ
It's goodbye
昔住んでた小さな部屋は
The small room where I used to live
今は誰かが住んでんだ
is now lived in by someone else.
君に言われたひどい言葉も
Even the harsh words you said to me,
無駄な気がした毎日も
and the days that felt like a waste,
あの時こうしてれば
if only I had done that back then,
あの日に戻れれば
if only I could return to that day,
あの頃の僕にはもう戻れないよ
I can't return to the way I was back then anymore.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a relaxed happiness
だらっと続いたとする
were to drag on continuously,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
surely a bad seed would sprout...
もう さよならなんだ
and it would already be goodbye.
寒い冬の冷えた缶コーヒー
A cold canned coffee in the freezing winter,
虹色の長いマフラー
a long, rainbow-colored scarf,
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
running through the back alley,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a relaxed happiness
だらっと続いたとする
were to drag on continuously,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して<
surely a bad seed would sprout...
もう さよならなんだ
and it would already be goodbye...
なんだ
goodbye...
さよなら それもいいさ
Goodbye, that's fine too.
どこかで元気でやれよ
Be well, wherever you are.
さよなら 僕もどうにかやるさ
Goodbye, I'll manage somehow too.
さよなら そうするよ
Goodbye, that's what I'll do.
はい。はい。はい、ということで、
Yes. Yes. Okay, with that,
「ソラニン」をお送りいたしました！いかがだったでしょうか？
I performed "Solanin"! How did you like it?
いや、あの、見覚えがある方もいらっしゃるのでは、ないでしょうか？
I'm sure some of you might find this familiar.
これ、まあ、初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが、
Though some of you might be seeing this for the first time.
あの、FGの3Dお披露目の時にも、ええと、ギターの弾き語りをお披露目させていただいたんですけれども、
During the FG 3D debut, I also showed off my acoustic guitar playing...
その時よりは、レベルアップできていたでしょうか？
But do you think I've leveled up since then?
初めて多分、最初の頃に練習したのが「ソラニン」で、そこからずっと、ちゃんとできた姿をみんなに見せたかったので、この曲を選びました。
Probably the first song I ever practiced was "Solanin," and I wanted to show everyone how much better I've gotten, so I chose this song.
そしてですね、ギター、ちはの音だけじゃなくて、もう一本ソロとか、ベースがあったと思うんですが、
Also, there wasn't just Chihaya's guitar, but also another guitar solo and bass track.
それはですね、ちはのギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
That's because my guitar teacher played them with me!
なんか、レッスンの時にセッションしてたら「え、めっちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、
We were jamming during a lesson and thought, "Wow, isn't this super cool?"
「先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんか？」って言って、
So I asked, "Teacher, would you like to play along with me?"
一緒に弾いていただきました。ありがとうございました！
And we played together. Thank you so much!
ということでね、一旦ここまでの振り返りをして行こうかなと思いますよ。まずは、ゲストパートで1曲目が、つ...
So, let's take a moment to look back on what we've done so far. First, for the guest part, the first song was...
トワハチでGO！ ファイティンDreamer！
We did TowaHachi de GO! Fighting Dreamer!
しました！どうですか？
We did it! How was it?
やっぱり1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って、
I wanted to kick things off with a blast for the first song,
トワハチでね、めちゃ盛り上がる曲を選びました。
so I chose a super exciting song for TowaHachi.
もう先輩たちのぶち上げがカッコよくて、ちーちゃんも「頑張るぞ！」ってなったので、
The seniors' hype was so cool, it made me go "I'm gonna do my best too!"
楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
So I hope you enjoyed it.
そして、2曲目はトワ様と「カルマ」を歌いました。
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama.
やっぱトワ様の低音が大好きなんで、
I really love Towa-sama's low register,
ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね、すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただきました。
so I asked her to sing with me in the original key, which is really low.
トワ様ありがとうございました！めっちゃカッコよかったです！
Thank you so much, Towa-sama! It was super cool!
そして、3曲目がルイ先輩と「ジブンロック」。
And for the third song, "Jibun Rock" with Lui-senpai.
いやカッコよすぎない？ やっぱルイ先輩カッコよすぎない？ヤバいんですけど。
I mean, isn't that just too cool? Seriously, isn't Lui-senpai way too cool? It's amazing.
あの本当にルイ先輩のね、カッコいいちょっとこう、がなりの効いた、エッジの効いた声で、
I really wanted to sing this song with Lui-senpai's cool, growling, edgy voice,
歌いたいなと思って、この曲を選びました。超カッコよかったよね。
so that's why I chose it. It was incredibly cool, wasn't it?
そして、6曲目が「星座になれたら」を、
And for the sixth song, "Seiza ni Naretara"...
さっきね、ふじちゃんたちと一緒にワイワイした「星座になれたら」で。
...which I just performed excitedly with Fuji-chan and the others.
7曲目、激エモのね、にゃんちゃん、おかゆ先輩との、
And for the seventh song, the super emotional...
「打上花火」、どうでしたか？もうマジで…あの本当に、
..."Uchiage Hanabi" with Okayu-senpai, how was it?
おにぎりの皆さんには申し訳ないんですけれど、
I'm really sorry to all the Onigiri (Okayu's fans), but...
あの瞬間はちょっと自分、おかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりで、もう！ってやってしまいました。
at that moment, I kind of pretended to be Okayu-senpai's boyfriend, and went like, "Geez!"
もう、あの、最高でした。ありがとうございました本当に。
It was just, like, the best. Thank you so much, really.
お返しします。ありがとうございました。
I'll return her now. Thank you very much.
というね、エモエモな、
So we had that super emotional...
カッコいいからエモまでのパートがありましたが、楽しんでいただけてますか？
...part from cool to emotional. Are you guys enjoying it?
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな。
Let me take a look at the comments.
「エモすぎた」「泣いた」わかる！
"Too emotional," "I cried." I get it!
わかる、めちゃエモいよね！
I know, it's super emotional, right?
ちーはもなんかやりながら「エモすぎるこれ」と思ってやってましたよ。
I was thinking "This is too emotional" even while performing it!
ありがとう！めっちゃ良かったよね。
Thank you! It was really great, wasn't it?
さあ、ということでね、
All right, with that said...
ちょっとあの、ちーは喋らせると喋りすぎてしまうので、次のパートにいきたいんですが、
...if you let me keep talking, I'll talk way too much, so I'd like to move on to the next part.
ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
From here, we have some exciting news!
輪堂千早 誕生日記念2026グッズ販売の告知となります！
Announcements for Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Celebration 2026 Merchandise Sales!
生誕グッズが出るぞ！こちらをご覧ください。ドン！
Birthday merch is coming out! Please take a look at this. Bam!
[Visual: Chihaya Birthday Fes 2026]
はい！盛りだくさんですね！
Yes! There's so much stuff!
イラストは、とりだもの先生、ママに描いていただきました。ありがとうございます！
The illustration was drawn by Toridamono-sensei, my Mama! Thank you so much!
ギターをね、弾いてるライブのワンシーンをイメージして描いていただきました。いや、めっちゃカッコいいよね！
She drew it with the image of a live performance scene where I'm playing the guitar. Man, it's so cool, isn't it?
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Now let's look at the details. First is this one!
千早バースデーフェスTシャツ2026でございます！
It's the Chihaya Birthday Fes T-shirt 2026!
キービジュアルのイラスト全身を使用したカッコ可愛いTシャツです。
It's a cool and cute T-shirt using the full-body key visual illustration.
バンドTシャツっぽくしたくてね、ちょっとロゴとかイカつい感じにしてもらったので、
I wanted to make it look like a band T-shirt, so I had the logo designed to look a bit edgy and cool,
ぜひぜひライブ、ライブとか日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです。
so I'd love it if you wore it to live shows or just in your daily life.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this one!
ピックケースキーホルダーです！
It's a Pick Case Key Holder!
お気に入りのピックを入れておしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです。
It's a key holder that lets you carry your favorite picks in style.
キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品として付いています。ピックケースホルダーにはピックが1枚入る仕様です。
The key holder is the main item, and three picks are included as accessories. The case holds one pick.
あの、今回のために書いたサインとかロゴとか、
The set includes picks with the signature and logo I wrote for this occasion,
あとは「フラットアウト」っていうロゴ。
as well as the "Flatout" logo, which is also the title of this festival.
今回のあの、タイトルにもなってる「フラットアウト」のロゴが書かれてるピックがセットになっています。
The picks feature these designs.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this one!
ちはとお出かけバッグです！
It's the "Go Out with Chiiha" Bag!
前にポーチが付いていて、前のポーチをひっくり返すと中身を見せて推しバッグにチェンジできる、ちょっとね、機能性のあるバッグ、
It has a pouch on the front. If you flip the front pouch inside out, you can display your items and change it into an "oshi bag".
斜め掛けのバッグになっています。
It's designed as a crossbody bag.
いろんなところ、これで、お出かけしてください！
Please take this bag with you to all sorts of places!
そして、続いては、こちら！
And next is this one!
どこでもふぐたろうティッシュカバー！
It's the "Fugutaro Everywhere" Tissue Cover!
ふんわりとした質感のふぐたろうモチーフのティッシュカバーです。
It's a tissue cover featuring a Fugutaro motif with a soft texture.
え、可愛いよね！お家でも車でも職場でもふぐたろう連れていけます！
It's so cute, right? You can take Fugutaro with you to your home, car, or workplace!
そして続いては、こちら！
And next up is this!
シチュエーションボイスです！
It's a Situation Voice!
タイトルは「ライブリハーサルボイス」。
The title is "Live Rehearsal Voice."
ライブ前のリハーサルでドキドキ緊張している千早のシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので、
It's a situation voice of Chihaya feeling super nervous and excited before the live show,
ドキドキの緊張感をね、ぜひ聞きに来てください。
so please come listen to my pounding nervousness.
そして、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
And we also have a full set purchase bonus! Here it is!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードです。
It's a cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped printed message!
全部ね、直筆で千早がサインを書きますのでね、ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。
I'll be signing every single one by hand, so I'd be really happy if you bought the full set.
そして特典ボイス、タイトルは「ライブ後、君と」になります。
And the bonus voice title is "With You, After the Live."
先ほどのね、ボイスと合わせて聴くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので、
I think listening to it along with the previous voice will make it even more emotional,
ぜひこちらも聴いてみてください。
so please listen to this one as well.
改めて、フルセットはこちらになります。
To recap, here is the full set.
やっぱね、これ全部、Tシャツ着て、バッグ持って、キーホルダーつけて、
After all, if you wear the T-shirt, carry the bag, attach the key holder,
ふぐたろう持って、どこでも行ける「千早セット」千早セットなので、
and bring Fugutaro, it's a "Chihaya Set" that lets you go anywhere.
まあ、買うならフルセットの方がいいよね。
So, if you're buying, the full set is definitely the way to go.
21時、この後21時カートオープンとなりますので、
The cart opens at 21:00, right after this.
数量限定ではないので、ぜひね、あの、ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします。
They aren't limited in quantity, so I'd be very happy if you could take your time to purchase them. Thank you!
おねがいします
Please!
そして、皆様待望のお知らせがございます！
And now, we have an announcement you've all been waiting for!
こちら！
This is it!
なんと！凛堂千早ソロとして、初めてのオリ曲
Believe it or not, my very first solo original song as Rindo Chihaya,
「Flatout」がこの後24時、7月9日木曜日の0時
"Flatout," will be digitally released later tonight at midnight,
この後ですね、3時間ちょい後くらいからデジタルリリースされます！
well, technically at 0:00 on Thursday, July 9th, which is about 3 hours from now!
やったー！
Yay!
このポーズしてる。今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」は、オリ曲のタイトルでございました！
I'm doing this pose. "Flatout," which is also the title of this live stream, was the title of my original song!
えー、この配信が終わった後にMVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The MV will be released after this stream ends, so please look forward to it!
概要欄にね、あの、そのうち多分リンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うので、そちらもチェックしてみてください。
I think a link will probably be added to the description box sooner or later, so please check it out too.
えー新曲、この後やっぱり早速聴きたいですよね？この後、披露するので絶対に聴いてください。
Now, I'm sure you want to hear the new song right away, don't you? I'll be performing it next, so please make sure to listen to it.
最後まで、最後までね、チャンネルはそのままで見ていってくださいね。
Please stay tuned until the very end, and keep your channel right here.
以上、凛堂千早生誕祭2026のグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
And that's all for the merchandise and release information for Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Festival 2026!
みんな、買ってね！サブスクでも聴いてね！
Everyone, please buy them! And make sure to stream the song too!
はい、ということで、怒涛のお知らせコーナーでした。
Alright, so that was the whirlwind of announcements.
ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです。でも、まだまだあります。
From here on, the live performance is finally reaching its climax. But there is still more to come.
盛り上がる準備できてますか？最後一緒にぶち上げていこうね！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let's blow the roof off together at the end!
では、準備してきます。
Now, I'll go get ready.
会おう！そのチャンネルはそのままに。
See you! Keep your channel right here.
I wanna fly so high
Yeah, I know my wings are dried
「翼仰げば」って人は云う
People say, "Just look up at the wings"
その向こうにあるは無情
But what lies beyond is heartlessness
飛べる者 落ちる者
Those who can fly, those who fall
誰も見てない 気にも留めない
No one is watching, no one even cares
それでも飛び続けた
Yet I kept on flying
傷ついた言葉乗せ 運びたいから
Because I want to carry and deliver these wounded words
追いかけて届くよう
Chasing, hoping to reach you
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
We flap our wings with all our heart
問いかけて嘆いた夜
The night I questioned and lamented
故郷（まち）は一層輝いて
My hometown shined even brighter
ワタリドリの様に今 旅に立つよ
Now I set out on a journey like a migratory bird
ありもしないストーリーを 描いてみせるよ
A story that doesn't even exist, I will show you I can draw it
I wanna fly so far
Away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う
People sing, "You're not alone"
間違いじゃない 理想論でもない
It's not wrong, nor is it just an ideal theory
ただ頼って生きたくはない
I just don't want to live by relying on others
誰も聴いていない 気にも留めない
No one is listening, no one even cares
それでも歌い続けた
Yet I kept on singing
傷ついたあなたを 笑わせたいから
Because I want to make you, who are hurt, smile
追い風届けるよ
I will deliver a tailwind to you
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
We flap our wings with all our heart
遠い過去を背負ってた
I will carry you, who were burdened with a distant past,
あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
to the future
ワタリドリの様に今 群れをなして
Now like a migratory bird, we form a flock
大それた四重奏を 奏で終える日まで
Until the day we finish playing this grand quartet
All this time we come and we grow
Now it's time that we should go
But we both know that this is for sure
It's not the end of the world
We'll see you one day
追いかけて届くよう
Chasing, hoping to reach you
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
We flap our wings with all our heart
問いかけて嘆いた夜
The night I questioned and lamented
朝焼け色に染まっていく
It's being dyed in the colors of the morning glow
ワタリドリの様にいつか 舞い戻るよ
Like a migratory bird, one day I will fly back
ありもしないストーリーを
A story that doesn't even exist
いつかまた会う日まで
Until the day we meet again
...いつかまた会う日まで
...until the day we meet again
Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)
作詞：金丸佳史 作曲：中野領太 編曲：秋浦智裕
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanemaru / Composition: Ryota Nakano / Arrangement: Tomohiro Akiura
はい、ということで
So, anyway...
輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで見てくれたみんな本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone who has watched Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival up to this point!
えー、次が本当にラストの曲です。
So, next up is indeed the last song.
この曲はいつかみんなと現地で会って、
I hoped that we could sing this song at the very end when we eventually meet in person...
ライブができた時に最後に歌えたらいいなって、そんな思いで、千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
...and have a live concert, so it was made with many of Chihaya's feelings in mind.
千速の初めてのオリ曲、聴いてください。
Please listen to Chihaya's very first original song.
Flat out。
\"Flat out\".
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前三時
A melancholy refrain at 3 AM.
夢を見るには少し遅すぎたMidnight
Midnight was a little too late to dream.
言葉にならないままの想いが
Before the feelings that won't turn into words...
溢れだしてしまう前に
...start to overflow,
飛び出した部屋
I ran out of my room,
光を見たくて
wanting to see the light.
”どうせ”だなんて何度だって諦めようとしたって
Even if I tried to give up over and over again, saying \"it's useless anyway,\"
だけどきっと今日もそっと伸ばした手 あの星まで
I surely stretched my hand out gently to that star again today.
自分さえだませない嘘はもうやめて踏み込め
Stop the lies that can't even fool yourself, and take a step forward!
駆け抜けて 音も風も抜き去って
Run through, passing the sound and the wind,
迷いさえも振り切ってスピードを上げて
shaking off even the hesitation, speed up!
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I must go, beyond the night,
見たこともない世界へ
to a world I've never seen,
今最高速度で
now at top speed,
高鳴る方へ
towards the thrumming!
答えなんてなくたってただこうしていたいだけ
Even if there's no answer, I just want to stay like this,
未完成で完全な道の先まで 行ける信じて
believing I can go to the end of this imperfect, perfect road.
差し障りないように生きた日々
In the days lived to be harmless,
諦めの言い訳を探すのをやめて保存しよう
stop looking for excuses to give up.
もどかしい気持ち 窓の向こうに
Frustrating feelings, beyond the window,
輝くあの星みたいになりたかったんだ
I wanted to become like that shining star.
足りない物だらけだって どれだけ離されたって
Even if I'm full of missing things, no matter how far I'm separated,
止まればそこまでなんだ
if I stop, that's it!
進め 進め
Go forward, go forward!
未来を変える瞬間はいつかじゃなくて今なんだ
The moment to change the future is not someday, it's now!
進め 進め
Go forward, go forward,
先へ さあ
ahead, now!
もっと遠くまで
Even further...
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
...I will go to find out, Flat out!
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Run through, to that stage I saw in my dreams,
決して振り返らないでスピードを上げて保存しよう
never looking back, speed up!
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ保存しよう
I must go, beyond the night,
見たこともない世界へ
to a world I've never seen,
今最高速度で保存しよう
now at top speed,
信じる方へ
towards what I believe!
答えなんてなくたってただこうして
Even if there's no answer, just like this,
走り出したんだ 止まらないよ さあ
I started running, I won't stop, now!
あの星に届け
reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026 見ていただいて本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for watching Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival 2026!
これからもみんなと向こうの景色たくさん見に行きたいです！
From now on, I want to go see many sights beyond with everyone!
これからも千速のことを好きでいてついてきてくれたら嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you keep loving Chihaya and follow along!
本当に今日はありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for today!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you!
輪堂千夜生誕LIVE お越しいただきありがとうございます
[Text: Thank you for coming to Rindo Chiyah's Birthday LIVE!]
これからも走り続けるよ！！！ 今日は本当にありがとう
[Text: I will keep running forward! Thank you so much for today!]
揺れる境界線
The swaying boundary line
僕らを繋ぎ止めて
holds us together.
あの日の誓いも
Will even the vow from that day
いつしか色褪せていくの？
eventually fade away?
音も立てずに
Without making a sound,
崩れ去る世界で
in this crumbling world,
確かなものなんて
I used to think there wasn't
何一つ無いと思ってた
a single certain thing.
だけど君が
But because you...
手を伸ばしてくれたから
reached out your hand to me,
もう一度だけ
just once more,
信じてみようと思えたんだ
I felt like I could believe again.